<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Gatsby Starter Blog RSS Feed]]></title><description><![CDATA[A starter blog demonstrating what Gatsby can do.]]></description><link>https://gatsbystarterblogsource.gatsbyjs.io</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 19:25:53 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title><![CDATA[Deception City]]></title><description><![CDATA[What even is this? Deception City is a social deduction game (SDG) that I work on in my spare time, hosted over a Discord server that I own…]]></description><link>https://gatsbystarterblogsource.gatsbyjs.io/my-second-post/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://gatsbystarterblogsource.gatsbyjs.io/my-second-post/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;h3&gt;What even is this?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Deception City is a social deduction game (SDG) that I work on in my spare time, hosted over a Discord server that I own. The server has just recently reached 100 players, and I take great pride in how far it has come in its five years of existence. The server is, as of right now, on hiatus so that I may make changes to the server&apos;s balance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I run the server solely for the enjoyment of myself and others in the server to give us all something to do in our free time. I&apos;m always hoping to get more people involved.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[College Work]]></title><description><![CDATA[Classes I have 3 classes to do work in, those being Document Engineering, Introduction to Communication Competencies, Adult Psychopathology…]]></description><link>https://gatsbystarterblogsource.gatsbyjs.io/hello-world/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://gatsbystarterblogsource.gatsbyjs.io/hello-world/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;h3&gt;Classes&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have 3 classes to do work in, those being Document Engineering, Introduction to Communication Competencies, Adult Psychopathology, as well as weekly meetings with my advisors. I do work in all classes I attend (if somewhat slowly) and finish my assignments mostly on time. This first semester of college is decently easy, which is something I should be happy about.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Projects&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have currently done two large writing assignments in Communication Competencies, eight labs in Document Engineering, and have a major writing assignment for Psychopathology that I am working on.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[RPD]]></title><description><![CDATA[Again, what is this? RPD is another server I host on Discord, but this one is a somewhat-adjacent-to Dungeons & Dragons roleplay game that I…]]></description><link>https://gatsbystarterblogsource.gatsbyjs.io/new-beginnings/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://gatsbystarterblogsource.gatsbyjs.io/new-beginnings/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;h3&gt;Again, what is this?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;RPD is another server I host on Discord, but this one is a somewhat-adjacent-to Dungeons &amp;#x26; Dragons roleplay game that I run for a small group of my friends. I alongside the seven of them hold a session every weekend for fun using a story that I&apos;ve created.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>